locators-online.org 2008-06-16

# Locators Online -

The web site you are viewing \- http://www.locators-online.org,  is owned and operated by Locators Online. We understand that visitors to this site may be concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we use that information. This Policy addresses those concerns. If you have any questions please do not hesitate to contact us. 

**Policy**  
Locators Online respects the privacy of its online visitors, and users of our family linking and tracking services. At this site, we do not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. We do not require you to register or provide information in order to view this site. 

Locators Online only gathers personally identifiable date, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, etc., when voluntarily and knowingly submitted by a visitor. For example, personally identifiable information is collected in order to respond to a family liking and tracking request via our eLocate form. This information is used solely by Locators Online or other entities who are involved in the operation of this site for internal purposes. Databases containing this information are never sold to third parties. We will only share personally identifiable information with third parties when (1) the person submitting the information authorizes us to share it; or (2) we are required to do so by law. 

**Are our Databases secure?**   
Yes. Information transmitted to Locators Online by e-mail, phone, fax or via our web site, is automatically added to a central database that is kept in our headquarters in Northern Cyprus. This database is not directly accessible via the internet. We use high grade encryption and the https security protocol to communicate with your browser software. This method is the industry standard security protocol, which makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept the information you send us. 

**How do we use "Cookies"?**   
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by the Locators Online web site through the use of "cookies." "Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile data  that will allow content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files. Cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. 

**Note to Parents  
**Locators Online welcomes children to our site to learn more about our organisation and, where appropriate, find opportunities to serve the global community through Locators Online volunteer activities. We encourage this to be done only with their parent's knowledge and supervision, as our web site contains forms via which personally identifiable information may be gathered.
